The rush is on!
Rush Hour 3 is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Brett Ratner.
After a botched assassination attempt, the mismatched duo finds themselves in Paris, struggling to retrieve a
precious list of names, as the murderous crime syndicate's henchmen try their best to stop them.
Once more, Lee and Carter must fight their way through dangerous gangsters;
however, this time, the past has come back to haunt Lee.
Will the boys get the job done once and for all?
Yan Naing Lee, played by Jackie Chan.
James Carter, played by Chris Tucker.
Kenji, played by Hiroyuki Sanada.
Varden Reynard, played by Max von Sydow.
George, played by Yvan Attal.
Det. Revi, played by Roman Polanski.
Rush Hour 3 is a 2007 American buddy cop  action comedy film
directed by Brett Ratner, written by Jeff Nathanson.
It is the third installment in the Rush Hour
franchise and sequel to Rush Hour 2.
Jackie Chan, Chris Tucker, Tzi Ma and Philip Baker Hall reprise their roles from the previous
films with Hiroyuki Sanada, Youki Kudoh and Max von Sydow joining the cast.
The story centers on Hong Kong Police Force (HKPF) Chief Inspector Lee (Chan) and Los Angeles Police Department (LAPD)
Detective James Carter (Tucker) tracking an assassin (Sanada) to Paris to unravel a mystery about the Chinese triads.
Announced on May 7, 2006, filming began on July 4 on
location in Paris and Los Angeles.
Released on August 10, 2007, the film grossed $258 million worldwide against a
production budget of $125–180 million but was not well received from critics.
It was also filmed in California and New York.
It was the last film scored by prolific film composer Lalo Schifrin.
A sequel is in development with Brett Ratner returning to direct.
The film explores themes of martial arts, ambassador, cop, los
angeles, california, interracial friendship.
The tone is lighthearted.